<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <Constellation_Sagittarius.label>Constellation of Sagittarius</Constellation_Sagittarius.label>
  <Constellation_Sagittarius.description>The constellation of Sagittarius shone in the sky. This event instills courage in your shooters. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Sagittarius.description>
  
  
  <Constellation_Hercules.label>Constellation of Hercules</Constellation_Hercules.label>
  <Constellation_Hercules.description>The constellation of Hercules shone in the sky. This event instills courage and independence in the hearts of your warriors. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Hercules.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Build.label>Constellation of Nagonik</Constellation_Build.label>
  <Constellation_Build.description>The constellation of Nagon shone in the sky. This event instills the spirit of professionalism in your builders. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Build.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Art.label>Painter Constellation</Constellation_Art.label>
  <Constellation_Art.description>In the sky the constellation of the Painter shone. This event inspires the spirit of creativity in your masters. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Art.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Animals.label>Constellation of Big Dog</Constellation_Animals.label>
  <Constellation_Animals.description>In the sky the constellation of the Big Dog has shone. This event instills the spirit of confidence in your stockbreeder's. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Animals.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Plant.label>Constellation of Bootes</Constellation_Plant.label>
  <Constellation_Plant.description>In the sky, the constellation Bootes shone. This event instills the spirit of peace in your farmers. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Plant.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Social.label>Constellation of Dolphin</Constellation_Social.label>
  <Constellation_Social.description>The constellation of the Dolphin shone in the sky. This event inspires your merchants. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Social.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Craft.label>Constellation of Forge Hephaestus</Constellation_Craft.label>
  <Constellation_Craft.description>The constellation Forge Hephaestus shone in the sky. This event ignites the excitement in the eyes of your artisans. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Craft.description>
  
    
    <Constellation_Mining.label>Constellation of Table Mountain</Constellation_Mining.label>
  <Constellation_Mining.description>Constellation Table Mountain shone in the sky.  this event illuminate way your miners. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Mining.description>
  
    
    <Constellation_Cooking.label>Constellation of Bowl</Constellation_Cooking.label>
  <Constellation_Cooking.description>In the sky, the constellation Bowl shone. This event opens the culinary secrets to your cooks. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Cooking.description>
  
    
    <Constellation_Medicine.label>Constellation of Ophiuchus</Constellation_Medicine.label>
  <Constellation_Medicine.description>The constellation Ophiuchus shone in the sky. This event reveals the secrets of surgery to your doctors. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Medicine.description>
  
    
    <Constellation_Intellectual.label>Constellation Eagle</Constellation_Intellectual.label>
  <Constellation_Intellectual.description>In the sky, the constellation of the Eagle shone. This event inspires a thirst for knowledge to your scientists. Every creature feels a surge of strength.</Constellation_Intellectual.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Shield.label>Constellation of Shield</Constellation_Shield.label>
  <Constellation_Shield.description>The constellation Shield appeared in the sky. This event hides your gaze from the truth. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Shield.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Lynx.label>Constellation of Lynx</Constellation_Lynx.label>
  <Constellation_Lynx.description>Lynx constellation appeared in the sky. Targets elude you. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Lynx.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Triangle.label>Constellation of Triangle</Constellation_Triangle.label>
  <Constellation_Triangle.description>The constellation of the Triangle appeared in the sky. You can not understand your own construction drawings. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Triangle.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Clock.label>Constellation of Clock</Constellation_Clock.label>
  <Constellation_Clock.description>You notice the lack of time for creativity. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Clock.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Hydra.label>Constellation of Hydra</Constellation_Hydra.label>
  <Constellation_Hydra.description>You see your helplessness before the animals. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Hydra.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Corvus.label>Constellation of Corvus</Constellation_Corvus.label>
  <Constellation_Corvus.description>You notice how your crop is destroyed by birds. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Corvus.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Indian.label>Constellation of Indian</Constellation_Indian.label>
  <Constellation_Indian.description>You are be aloof. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Indian.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Eridan.label>Constellation of Eridan</Constellation_Eridan.label>
  <Constellation_Eridan.description>Thoughts are confused, hands do not obey you. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Eridan.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Taurus.label>Constellation of Taurus</Constellation_Taurus.label>
  <Constellation_Taurus.description>Rocks does not give in to you. You are lost in the mountain tunnels. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Taurus.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Coma.label>Constellation of Virgo</Constellation_Coma.label>
  <Constellation_Coma.description>It seems you have stopped remembering your own recipes. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Coma.description>
  
  
    <Constellation_Snake.label>Constellation of Snake</Constellation_Snake.label>
  <Constellation_Snake.description>Your surgery skills leave you. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Snake.description>
  
  
   <Constellation_Octans.label>Constellation of Octans</Constellation_Octans.label>
  <Constellation_Octans.description>The Octant illuminates you with its dim light. You can not find the strength to research. Every creature feels a breakdown.</Constellation_Octans.description>
  
</LanguageData>