<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <QuestFail>Quest {0} failed</QuestFail>
  <QuestSuccess>Quest {0} completed</QuestSuccess>
  <QuestTimeout>Time to complete the quest {0} has expired</QuestTimeout>
  <UnlimitedTime>Time left: unlimited</UnlimitedTime>
  <QuestTimer>Time left: {0} days</QuestTimer>
  <JumpToLocation>Jump to location ({0})</JumpToLocation>
  <QuestRewards>Reward</QuestRewards>
  <AdditionalQuestContent>Additionally</AdditionalQuestContent>

  <OpenCommsGeo>Use console</OpenCommsGeo>
  <OpenCommsGeoNoPower>Use console [no power]</OpenCommsGeoNoPower>
  
  <EventsCommTab>Active events</EventsCommTab>
  <QuestsCommTab>Quests</QuestsCommTab>
  <InteractionCommTab>Communication</InteractionCommTab>
  
  <RelatedEventCom>Related event: {0}</RelatedEventCom>
  <FactionComm>Faction: {0}</FactionComm>
  <NoEventComm>Related event: no</NoEventComm>
  <NoFactionComm>Faction: no</NoFactionComm>

  <HelpingFactionsList>\nHelp: </HelpingFactionsList>
  <SupportFullDoomsday>Help is fully staffed. You can not take more frctions.</SupportFullDoomsday>
  <NoHelpDoomsday>Will not help</NoHelpDoomsday>
  <UnknownDoomsdayStatus>Not known</UnknownDoomsdayStatus>
  <HelpDoomsday>Will help</HelpDoomsday>
  <DiscussWithOtherFactions>Discuss the event with other factions.</DiscussWithOtherFactions>
  <DoomsdayCardLabel>End of the world</DoomsdayCardLabel>
  <DoomsdayDesc>The {0} faction gathered to arrange a kawabanga on this planet. We can try to collect the missing amount, or maybe other factions will be able to help in the raid on their base?</DoomsdayDesc>
  <AdditionalContent>Additional Information</AdditionalContent>
  
  <CommOption_GetHelp_Label>Ask for help (left: {0})</CommOption_GetHelp_Label>
  <Help_AskResoucesTitle>Resources sent</Help_AskResoucesTitle>
  <Help_AskResouces>The {0} faction remembers its duty and sends you the resources that it was able to collect. {1}</Help_AskResouces>
  <Help_AskPowerTitle>Help was sent</Help_AskPowerTitle>
  <Help_AskPower>The faction {0} remembers its duty and sends you a group of its fighters to support your settlement.</Help_AskPower>
  <UsingCaravan>The faction technology does not allow it to use capsules, so they sent a caravan.</UsingCaravan>
  <UsingCapsules>Support was sent by capsules.</UsingCapsules>
  <GiftHasBeenDroppedTitle>Resources transferred</GiftHasBeenDroppedTitle>
  <GiftHasBeenDropped>Resources left close to your colony. (click that go)</GiftHasBeenDropped>
  <AssistCaravan_GifterArrivedTitle>Friendly squad arrived</AssistCaravan_GifterArrivedTitle>
  <AssistCaravan_GifterArrived>A friendly squad arrived at your request. They will leave things near your colony.</AssistCaravan_GifterArrived>
  
  <ClimateBombTitle>Climate bomb</ClimateBombTitle>
  <ClimateBombDesc>We found a climate bomb. Thoughts in my head mixed up. Who and why left it on this planet is not clear, but we need to neutralize it, if we don’t want the next couple of seasons to have anything happen to our climate. \n\nWe need to assemble a good squad, most likely there will be enemy factions, probably will be tied the battle.
</ClimateBombDesc>
  
  <Comm_MassiveFireTitle>Massive fires</Comm_MassiveFireTitle>
  <Comm_MassiveFireDesc>Near our settlement a fire broke out, probably caused by the weather. With every minute it inflames more and more. It is fraught with ignition of neighboring lands, including ours. \nWe can hope for rain or try to put it out ourselves.</Comm_MassiveFireDesc>
  
  <Comm_ShipCrashTitle>Ship crash</Comm_ShipCrashTitle>
  <Comm_ShipCrashDesc>We saw a ship crash. In appearance - a general purpose ship. When it fell, it fell apart, some of them were large, some small. These are probably cargo and living compartments. \nThe ship's parts are scattered all over the planet. The plating of the ship is made of plastal, so probably a lot could have survived. You can form a caravan and see what remains of the compartments, taking the contents yourself. True, such a profit is likely to attract uninvited guests.</Comm_ShipCrashDesc>
  
  <Comm_SiegeCampTitle>Siege Camp</Comm_SiegeCampTitle>
  <Comm_SiegeCampDesc>Not far from us the camp of gangsters was founded. They have mortars and a desire to kill us. They will attack us at short intervals, simultaneously rebuilding their camp and increasing their combat power. We need to destroy him as soon as possible, before he becomes a real problem.</Comm_SiegeCampDesc>
  
  <EmailMessage_From>From: {0}</EmailMessage_From>
  <EmailMessage_To>To: {0}</EmailMessage_To>
  <EmailMessageReceivedTitle>Message received</EmailMessageReceivedTitle>
  <EmailMessageReceived>You have received a message from {0} on the topic {1}. You can view it in the mailbox, in Geoscape.</EmailMessageReceived>
  <DeleteMessage>Delete message</DeleteMessage>
  
  <ScoutingComp_InfoTitle>Greetings I am sending you information from our intelligence officers that they were able to collect for your settlement. The report indicates the danger and the estimated time.\n\n</ScoutingComp_InfoTitle>
  <ScoutingComp_ThreatKnown>(Threat: {0})</ScoutingComp_ThreatKnown>
  <ScoutingComp_ThreatUnknown>(Threat level unknown)</ScoutingComp_ThreatUnknown>
  <ScoutingComp_CommingTime> estimated time of arrival {0} (days)</ScoutingComp_CommingTime>
  <ScoutingComp_NoThreatsInfoTitle>Greetings After several days of absence, our scouts finally returned. They did not detect any looming threats.</ScoutingComp_NoThreatsInfoTitle>
  <ScoutingComp_Subject>Intelligence report</ScoutingComp_Subject>
  
</LanguageData>