<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<QuestPrefix>Quest</QuestPrefix>

	<Quest_RequiredItems>Requested resources</Quest_RequiredItems>
	<Quest_HelpItems_Site>Place of transfer of resources</Quest_HelpItems_Site>
	<HowToCheckReqList>To view a list of required items, open detailed information.</HowToCheckReqList>
	<HelpResourcesDescriptionTitle>Faction {0} requested resources. We need to send a caravan with the necessary resources to this point in order to transfer them.

List of required resources:</HelpResourcesDescriptionTitle>
	<GiveItemsSuccessTitle>Items transferred</GiveItemsSuccessTitle>
	<GiveItemsSuccess>You have successfully transferred resources. The reward was sent to your base by transport containers.</GiveItemsSuccess>
	<GiveItemsSuccess2>You have successfully transferred resources. The award was given to your caravan.</GiveItemsSuccess2>
	<NotEnoughItemsToQuest>Not enough items</NotEnoughItemsToQuest>
	<GiveItemsOption>Transfer resources</GiveItemsOption>
	
	<Quest_HelpItems_Label>Request for resources</Quest_HelpItems_Label>
	<Quest_HelpItems_Description>The leader of the {0} faction contacts you and tells you that they are going to expand their settlement, but they don’t have so many available resources. They request some resources from you in the hope that you have them and you can transfer them. Instead, they will give what they have in abundance. \nWe can form a caravan with the necessary items and send it to them.
</Quest_HelpItems_Description>

	<HowToGivePawns>To assist the settlement, send a caravan with the required number of pawns ({0}) to the construction site. \nConstruction time: {1}</HowToGivePawns>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Label>Construction of a new settlement</Quest_BuildNewBase_Label>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Description>The faction {0} is about to change their place of residence. The leader of the faction {1} explains this by the lack of basic resources in the current place of residence, as well as poor landscape and unpleasant weather. Building a new base is costly and long, fortunately, they have enough resources, but there are no pawns capable of holding a hammer. In order not to delay the construction, he asks you for a few of your pawns to assist in the construction. \n\nConstruction may take several days. At this time, your pawns will be unavailable, and upon completion of construction you will receive an award and your pawns.
</Quest_BuildNewBase_Description>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Place>Construction site {0}</Quest_BuildNewBase_Place>
	<NotEnoughPawnsToHelp>Not enough pawns in the caravan</NotEnoughPawnsToHelp>
	<HelpStartedTitle>Construction started</HelpStartedTitle>
	<HelpStarted>You have come to the construction site of a new settlement base. According to preliminary calculations, the construction will take {0} days, after which your pawns will return to you again.</HelpStarted>
	<BuildingAlreadyStarted>Construction has already begun</BuildingAlreadyStarted>
	<Quest_HelpWithBuilding_Option>To help</Quest_HelpWithBuilding_Option>
	<PawnsRequired>Pawns required: {0}</PawnsRequired>
	<BuildingSeccessEndTitle>Construction completed</BuildingSeccessEndTitle>
	<BuildingSeccessEnd>Construction of settlement for {0} is over. They thank you for their help and notify you that you can now ask them to help you in a difficult situation with resources or military help. (You can request through the Geoscape)
</BuildingSeccessEnd>

	<Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_CardLabel>Attack on a friendly settlement</Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_CardLabel>
	<Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_Description>The leader of the {0} allied faction {1} reports that their scouts noticed an approaching threat in the form of an enemy raid on their settlement. At the moment, most of their fighters on the mission, which, unfortunately, can not tell you. \nThey ask you to help them repel this attack. For this, they will be able to provide you with intelligence information from time to time. \n\nTo help a settlement repel an attack, collect a caravan with everything you need and head to the attack point on the map. \nThe reward depends on the number of surviving settlers of the allied settlement.
</Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_Description>
	<ScoutComp_GiveTitle>Intelligence agreement</ScoutComp_GiveTitle>
	<ScoutComp_Give>You have signed an intelligence agreement with the {0} faction, whereby they will provide intelligence data every {1} days for {2} days that may contain (depending on the success of the intelligence) information about imminent threats.</ScoutComp_Give>
	<ScoutComp_AlreadyGiveTitle>Intelligence agreement</ScoutComp_AlreadyGiveTitle>
	<ScoutComp_AlreadyGive>The agreement with faction {0} has already been signed, so it has been extended for {1} days.</ScoutComp_AlreadyGive>
	
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CardLabel>Missing settlers</Quest_MissingPeople_CardLabel>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Description>The leader of the faction {0} contacted us and reported that a couple of days ago a small group of their settlers went on a journey to get resources. Estimated time of their journey was estimated at {1} days. More than {2} days passed, but the settlers never returned. Attempts to get in touch have failed and they are worried that the settlers might get lost or be attacked. \nThe food intakes they had enough will last for about {3} days, after which they will starve. He asks us to find the missing settlers and return them to them.</Quest_MissingPeople_Description>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabel>Potential Settlers Place</Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabel>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString>Potential place for lost settlers. \nFood will end in: {0} (days)</Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString>
	<Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action>Inspect the place</Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFailTitle>Nothing found</Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFailTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFail>We arrived at the place. Wandering around the neighborhood, we looked into every corner, but did not find any traces of the settlers. Probably, we should check another place (the new place is marked on the map)</Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFail>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMapTitle>Missing settlers</Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMapTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMap>As soon as we entered the territory, we saw a small camp with a couple of settlers, who seem to be about to weaken. We told them that we came for them. In their eyes, there was a desire to live, but as soon as we were ready to leave, a detachment of enemy soldiers appeared on the opposite side. We will have to deal with them first, but we need to remember why we are here.</Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMap>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2Title>Caravan formed and can be sent</Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2Title>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2>We were able to repel the attack. It now remains only to escort the settlers home, for this we have {0}. If after this period we do not deliver them, then we will be condemned as thieves (take the caravan to the marked settlement base)</Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_End>You got to the Allied settlement.\n</Quest_MissingPeople_End>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndFull>\nYou managed to bring all the settlers alive, for which the faction {0} is very grateful to you.</Quest_MissingPeople_EndFull>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndPart>\nYou tell with what difficulties you had to face, that the settlers who died on the way were worthy and they can be proud of them.</Quest_MissingPeople_EndPart>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Fiasko>\nYou came with nothing. The leader of the {0} faction is very upset. One of the colonists is trying to calm him down, but he pushes him away and walks away.</Quest_MissingPeople_Fiasko>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndQuest>Quest result</Quest_MissingPeople_EndQuest>
	<Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action2>Transfer settlers</Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action2>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_ThiefTitle>Prosecution</Quest_MissingPeople_ThiefTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Thief>You did not return the surviving settlers in time, and those that were rescued returned on their own. They told their leader about this, which is why he accused you of harboring their settlers. All agreements that existed between you were broken.</Quest_MissingPeople_Thief>

	<Quest_TradeRequestComp_CardLabel>Trade request</Quest_TradeRequestComp_CardLabel>
	<Quest_BanditCamp_CardLabel>Bandit camp</Quest_BanditCamp_CardLabel>
	
	<Quest_KillLeader_CardLabel>Order to kill an enemy leader</Quest_KillLeader_CardLabel>
	<Quest_KillLeader_Description>{0} talks about the enemy leader-dictator {1} from faction {2}, who may threaten of their settlement and asks you to eliminate it. He marked the place on the world map.
The information that an assassination attempt is being prepared for him could already have been scattered around all edges of the world, therefore, it is necessary to act as soon as possible.</Quest_KillLeader_Description>
	<Quest_KillLeader_PlaceLabel>Target location</Quest_KillLeader_PlaceLabel>
	
</LanguageData>