<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <SuperHeatWave.label>Extreme heat</SuperHeatWave.label>
  <SuperHeatWave.description>Heavy duty heat wave overtook the planet. The temperature can rise to 100 degrees Celsius!</SuperHeatWave.description>
  <SuperHeatWave.endMessage>Extreme heat has passed.</SuperHeatWave.endMessage>

  <BoulderMassHit.label>Meteor Rain</BoulderMassHit.label>
  <BoulderMassHit.description>Meteor Rain! For some time, meteorites will fall to the ground.</BoulderMassHit.description>
  <BoulderMassHit.endMessage>It seems to be all...</BoulderMassHit.endMessage>

  <Endlessday.label>Endless day</Endlessday.label>
  <Endlessday.description>Because of the powerful flash of a distant star on the planet now is the day. At night too.</Endlessday.description>
  <Endlessday.endMessage>The cycle of day and night returned to normal</Endlessday.endMessage>
  
  <LeanAtmosphere.label>Lean atmosphere</LeanAtmosphere.label>
  <LeanAtmosphere.description>Due to the release of the colossal amount of energy of a star exploding in the distance, a part of the planet’s atmosphere has burnt out. This has significantly changed the local climatic conditions. The range of temperature fluctuations has increased.</LeanAtmosphere.description>
  <LeanAtmosphere.endMessage></LeanAtmosphere.endMessage>
  
  <RadiationFon.label>Increased Radiation</RadiationFon.label>
  <RadiationFon.description>Due to the large number of ozone holes, cosmic radiation easily passes through the atmosphere. Frequent presence on the open area is fraught with radiation.</RadiationFon.description>
  <RadiationFon.endMessage></RadiationFon.endMessage>
  
  <NoSun.label>No sun</NoSun.label>
  <NoSun.description>In this system, there are no stars that can heat and illuminate the planets. Endless darkness and extremely low temperatures are ensured.</NoSun.description>
  <NoSun.endMessage></NoSun.endMessage>
  
  <DenseAtmosphere.label>Dense Atmosphere</DenseAtmosphere.label>
  <DenseAtmosphere.description>The planet has a very dense atmosphere, which leads to a greenhouse effect</DenseAtmosphere.description>
  <DenseAtmosphere.endMessage></DenseAtmosphere.endMessage>
  
  <IceStorm.label>Ice Storm</IceStorm.label>
  <IceStorm.description>An ice storm overtook you. This storm carries incredible low temperatures and ice fragments. Do not leave the house</IceStorm.description>
  <IceStorm.endMessage>The ice storm has stopped</IceStorm.endMessage>
  
  <HeavyAir.label>Heavy Air</HeavyAir.label>
  <HeavyAir.description>The air flow brought a large amount of heavy gases, they make breathing difficult and poison the body, you need to wait a couple of days</HeavyAir.description>
  <HeavyAir.endMessage>It seems the bulk of the heavy elements have been blown away</HeavyAir.endMessage>
   
  <SandStorm.label>Sand storm</SandStorm.label>
  <SandStorm.description>A sandstorm is coming. During this time, will be reduced visibility, speed</SandStorm.description>
  <SandStorm.endMessage>Sand storm is over</SandStorm.endMessage>
  
  <ClimateChaos.label>Climate chaos</ClimateChaos.label>
  <ClimateChaos.description>Due to the powerful release of energy, a climatic shift has occurred. The constant change of weather and weather disasters.</ClimateChaos.description>
  <ClimateChaos.endMessage>The weather returns to normal</ClimateChaos.endMessage>  
   
  <IonizedAtmosphere.label>Ionized atmosphere</IonizedAtmosphere.label>
  <IonizedAtmosphere.description>The ionosphere layer is significantly larger than ever. This increases the chance of thunderstorms.</IonizedAtmosphere.description>
  <IonizedAtmosphere.endMessage>The size of the ionosphere has decreased</IonizedAtmosphere.endMessage>  
   
  <Earthquake.label>Earthquake</Earthquake.label>
  <Earthquake.description>An earthquake began, everyone in the shelter!</Earthquake.description>
  <Earthquake.endMessage>Earthquake over</Earthquake.endMessage> 
   
</LanguageData>