<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
 
  <ColdFusionReactor.label>Cold fusion reactor</ColdFusionReactor.label>
  <ColdFusionReactor.description>A reactor operating in uranium, but based on the principle of cold fusion. Almost does not emit heat, but it is a good source of energy.</ColdFusionReactor.description>
  <ColdFusionReactorHeath.label>Cold fusion reactor heart</ColdFusionReactorHeath.label>
  <ColdFusionReactorHeath.description>The main part of the cold fusion reactor. With the help of it, it will be possible to modernize a nuclear reactor in order to obtain a new, more perfect source of energy.</ColdFusionReactorHeath.description>

  <ArcReactor.label>Arc reactor</ArcReactor.label>
  <ArcReactor.description>A reactor operating in uranium, but based on the principle of cold fusion. Almost does not emit heat, but it is a good source of energy.</ArcReactor.description>
  <PalladiumCore.label>Palladium core</PalladiumCore.label>
  <PalladiumCore.description>The main source of energy. Despite the radioactivity, the design of the reactor does not allow it to affect the environment.</PalladiumCore.description>
  <Enricher.label>Enricher</Enricher.label>
  <Enricher.description>Inflates to the core and core, enhancing the generation of energy.</Enricher.description>
  
  <ZeroPointReactor.label>Zero point reactor</ZeroPointReactor.label>
  <ZeroPointReactor.description>A reactor built by someone who has reached an incredible level of science. These generators extract vacuum energy, providing an almost unlimited supply of energy.</ZeroPointReactor.description>
  <VacuumTube.label>Vacuum tube</VacuumTube.label>
  <VacuumTube.description>The main part of the reactor, it generates energy.</VacuumTube.description>
  <VacuumStabilizer.label>Vacuum stabilizer</VacuumStabilizer.label>
  <VacuumStabilizer.description>Stabilizes pressure and creates zero electromagnetic radiation.</VacuumStabilizer.description>
  <VacuumPump.label>Vacuum pump</VacuumPump.label>
  <VacuumPump.description>A pump used to control the level of oxygen and its composition in the room. It is an important component for the operation of the zero point reactor.</VacuumPump.description>
  
  <SingularReactor.label>Singular reactor</SingularReactor.label>
  <SingularReactor.description>The source of energy, where microscopic black holes (collapsars) are used as the working medium. The principle of operation of such a reactor is the use of energy released during the evaporation of a black hole.</SingularReactor.description>
  <SuperMagnetNewGeneration.label>Super Magnet New Generation</SuperMagnetNewGeneration.label>
  <SuperMagnetNewGeneration.description>Supermagnet, from an unknown material that holds a black hole.</SuperMagnetNewGeneration.description>
  <QuantumConverter.label>Quantum converter</QuantumConverter.label>
  <QuantumConverter.description>The main component that converts (captures) radiation from the evaporation of a black hole and converts it into energy.</QuantumConverter.description>
  
</LanguageData>